I'm off!
I am Nitrna from Bolt. Nice to meet you.
Let's do it!
Okay, let's get a lip and an image for the one-shot.
First of all, let's start with the lip.
In general, these are the two guys.
Rip on his back.
In the image...
In the image scene, there's an earphone in here.
It's an old iPod.
It's a music character listening to a song on an old iPod.
First, Lip...
I'm going to have him sit right here.
It's a little bit like this.
And he's going to move around a little bit.
I don't want him to move too much.
Like you're in a coma.
I thought it'd be nice.
Hey!
ZENBU
Cea
So much.
I'm selfish.
A little bit I'm a music character, so it seems.
I missed this... what should I do?
I miss this...what was the name again?
iPod?
Folkman? Isn't this an iPod?
iPod.
I miss this.
Do I know you, Ayanan?
I don't know.
I'm from the generation. I'm from the generation when I was in elementary school.
It was an iPod. I don't know.
I miss it. These are wired earphones. Sometimes I wear them, but recently I've been using Bluetooth.
It's a beautiful day, but it's raining.
I was thinking, "What am I going to do now, I've been rained out," but she said, "My power will clear it up.
But it's a beautiful day, and I think it's warmer outside.
Thank you for watching!
Good night.
Idols are awesome!
The venue for today's re-release is here.
Can you see it? Good night, everyone.
Good night.
From now on...
Color the world
Radio Building
Good morning.
Yes, cut.
Yes, then, it's Ric-okay.
And the camera as it is.
With this setting, we'll get the image.
So, just like before.
But I'm going to start with the earphones.
Yes.
You can have them say a lot of things.
Let's look back as it is.
Let's look at the other side.
It's a little bit like looking into the distance with your hands.
You just took my radio exercises.
It was taken away.
Yes, it's perfect.
Doing radio calisthenics in such a big place.
We always start the Relieve 1 event in Porto with the radio exercises.
I'm sure the fans know that.
Yes!
Yes! Good morning. Good morning.
Please do.
Okay, then.
I'll have you sit here at first, holding the book.
You don't have to flip through it or read it during the lip.
It's like you're holding something.
I'll have you hold this book.
Shoes?
His shoes.
American.
Music that never fades
The sun's been hiding for a moment.
What do you mean?
That's funny.
Oh, I'm sorry.
That's weird.
Wait a minute.
Just now, Nano-chan said...
I was just telling her that I'm glad it's sunny today.
I just told her that I'm glad the weather was fine.
She's saying that she's glad it was sunny.
NANO-chan, who says that, is quite the rainy girl herself.
She says so herself.
Self-aware
She's aware of it.
Oh, sun!
Shine your light on me!
The person you see before you is actually...
Ah, there is indeed. Horses.
But how many horses are there?
There are quite a few.
Ten.
Maybe 10 or less.
They are cute.
Horses.
I wonder what horses eat.
Pork sauce.
Oh, grass.
They get their fill of grass, don't they?
It's a huge diet, isn't it? For a person.
I can't do it.
I can't.
I like salad, but not all the time.
I'm so proud of you.
Let's put your eyes in that feeling, too.
Cut.
Someone said there are four kinds.
Really? Really?
I wouldn't ask first.
I didn't know first.
No, I didn't.
No, it wasn't.
It was so close.
I mean, they're looking at each other.
Oh, that's good, that's good, that's good, that's good.
Oh, that feels good.
What happens if I just fall back a little bit?
Just take your time.
Okay.
That's good. That's good.
Okay, thank you very much.
Cut is ok.
Thank you very much.
Okay, let's cut this scene here.